

ROHAN ADHIA

DATA ANALYST

Highly analytical and process-oriented data analyst with in-depth knowledge of database types; research methodologies; and big data capture, curation, manipulation and visualization. Furnish insights, analytics and business intelligence used to advance opportunity identification, process reengineering and corporate growth.

CONTACT

- Andheri East,
 Mumbai-400069
- rohan.adhia@gmail.com
- +91 9930494215
- in /rohanadhia
- https://rohanadhia.github.io/resume/

PERSONAL PROFILE

Extremely motivated to constantly develop my skills and grow professionally. I am confident in my excellent technical abilities, as they are responsible for evaluating sets of information and implementing appropriate solutions. My applicable technical experience and skills can include the following: programming and coding; ability to translate unstructured information into structured information

EDUCATION

Business Analytics & Data Science(2019) Edupristine

Ignite Program(2017)

Datamatics Business Solutions Limited

Bachelor of Science Information Technology (2014-15) Malini Kishor Sanghvi College of Commerce & Economics

Higher Secondary School (2010 – 2011) Vidyanidhi Jr. College

Secondary School Certificate (2007-2008)

St. Dominic Savio High School

SKILLS AND EXPERTISE

Excellent technical abilities, strong interpersonal skills, and effective project management abilities.

Intermediate MS Excel Mentor

Trained employees at Angel Broking Ltd on advanced features of MS Excel.

LANGUAGES & TECHNOLOGY

- · Data Analytics using R language.
- Python
- Java,
- ASP.NET with C#
- C & C++
- Google App Script -(Based on Javascript
- used to automate day to day tasks.)
- HTML/CSS
- JavaScript
- Front End Framework(Bootstrap)

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- GRAPHIC DESIGNING -Logo Designs
 Social Media Post Design Website Designing,
 Visiting Card Design Poster Design, etc.
- Music Production using FL Studio

HOBBIES

- Designing
- Music Production
- Reading
- · Web development
- · Watching web-series

- · Node JS JS Runtime Environment
- Express JS JS Framework for Node JS
- JQuery
- · APIs & Interfaces

SOFTWARES

- MS Excel & Google Sheets
- R Software
- · MS office
- Adobe Photoshop
- · Adobe Illustrator
- Visual Studio
- Canva
- Github

WORK EXPERIENCE

Angel Broking, Specialist - Analytics

SEPT 2018 - PRESENT

- Collaborating data from various branches & regions to ensure streamlined implementations of services, profiling source information and setting characteristics, and executing big data processes like parsing, filtering, text connotation, and enrichment.
- Responsible to look after business and financial data for the branch.
- Developed a live sales dashboard used for real time tracking and analysis of sales
- Mapping of client based on their region
- Analysis of various types sales and brokerage data for PAN india
- Designing and making analytical presentation for board meetings
- Automation of data to generate reports .

WNS Global Services, Senior Associate - Operations

SEPT 2017 - AUG 2018

- Responded to customer service enquiries/ complaints/suggestions/feedback via email within the assigned TAT.
- Identified and highlighted any concern affecting the brand.
- Provided accurate, valid and complete information by using the right methods and tools.

Datamatics Business Solutions Limited, Associate Web Research

JAN 2016 - MARCH 2017

- Worked on various projects into Data Research, Data Mining, & Data Cleansing
- Client interaction on regular basis
- Worked majorly with pilot projects & FTE projects
- Sampled data for new clients & provided efficient solutions working with the solutions desk
- Nominated & certified the Ignite program